{
    "subject": "resource/Soul_Khan",
    "predicate": "ontology/hometown",
    "object": "resource/United_States",
    "human_readable": "Soul Khan is from United States.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9442381262779236,
            "question": "Is Soul Khan American?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8375685214996338,
            "question": "From which nation does Soul Khan originate?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7539465427398682,
            "question": "Where is Soul Khan from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6857858300209045,
            "question": "What country is Soul Khan associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6491965651512146,
            "question": "What is the nationality of Soul Khan?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6450722217559814,
            "question": "To which nation does Soul Khan belong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6190164089202881,
            "question": "Where was Soul Khan born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6189612746238708,
            "question": "What is Soul Khan's nationality?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5017949342727661,
            "question": "Can you tell me about Soul Khan's place of origin?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4803341329097748,
            "question": "Soul Khan's home country is?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Soul Khan is from United States.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8914_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me about Soul Khan's place of origin?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8914_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Soul Khan's nationality?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8914_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where was Soul Khan born?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8914_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8914_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8914_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8914_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8914_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8914_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8914_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8914_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8914_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8914_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8914_63.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here's the response to the query:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\"output\": \"yes\"}\n```\n\nThe documents state, \"From the San Fernando Valley, but long ensconced in the New York rap scene, Soul Khan has become a critical favorite by making sincere music.\" This indicates that Soul Khan is indeed from the United States."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {'output': 'yes'}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}